NEFEDOV KIRILL

https://t.me/zesshi_sec \leq Moscow, Russia

shalltear_ziegler@mail.ru \langle linkedin.com/in/kirill-nefedov-zesshi \langle https://github.com/Zesshhi

OBJECTIVE

Python Middle Developer with 2 years of experience with Django, DRF and FastAPI frameworks. I like learning new technologies and reading tech books like Grokking Algorithms or Clean Code. I am also easy to fit into any team and find common language easily, quite good at decomposing a subject area

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Technologies, Moscow Witte University

2019 - 2023

SKILLS

Tech Languages Python, HTML, CSS, JS

Frameworks Django, DRF, FastAPI, Bootstrap

Tech tools PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis, Celery, Docker, RabbitMQ, Nginx, SQLAlchemy, Linux, Git

Languages Russian: Fluent, English: Upper-Intermediate, Japanese: Beginner

EXPERIENCE

Junior Backend Developer

July 2022 - January 2023

OffConcern

- Creating the architecture of the application, database
- Working with own API, working with JWT
- Working with servers: creating, configuring, LXS, docker, Nginx, gunicorn
- Creating microservices using Flask and SQLAlchemy

Junior+ FullStack Developer

Unica Engineering Corp.

January 2023 - August 2023 Moscow, Russia

- Created web application on integration with 1C for customers who can have access to their 1C trough via Browser
- Working with requests from 1C: requests, requests-cache processing, synchronization, working with parameters
- Working with json: Parsing, writing data into models and outputting data from JSON directly into a template

Middle Software Developer

August 2023 - Present

Russia, Moscow

- Developed bunch of microservices on FastAPI
- Maintaining the already existing code on Django and DRF

PROJECTS

VTB Bank

Qlubok QLUBOK Business Card Constructor is a powerful tool that allows you to design and customize your business cards according to your preferences.

Unica B2B Web application based on integration with 1C, which allows customers and contractors to interact with the accounting system of our company without access to 1C. The web-applications I implement allow you to display and change information directly in 1C

Business Conveyor Development of microservices on FastAPI that communicate with each other via Kafka using MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Keycloak for auth, Sentry for bugs control, Celery and Redis for occasional tasks. The main purpose of these microservices is to create a convenient and understandable web application for accountants and bank clients (LLC or Sole Proprietor), which allows to conveniently control and fill in accounting documents and reports.